So, with the accelerate, right,
we are able to sync this right to this
site. It's only one way,
and also within the DDP have their own
portal, right,
taking in tickets from this site to the
excelate, and also internal, I mean...
From other sources internally, OK,
so they have their own dashboard,
so Nirmala and I came up with,
so we want to combine this right,
the requirements from both this dashboard,
right,
and the requirements we we we we provided
to Yael and Mark to consolidate it,
so we basically the requirements coming
from.
No,
a combination of a combined from this is
a super set requirement, OK?
Okay.
So, so this is this is the architecture,
right? So, and and.
Mhm.
Some of these requirements,
the dashboard here, they are overlapping,
some are not.
So, the requirement that we, we,
we provided is, you know,
a combination of both sides is a superset,
right?
That's that's the one that we sent to you,
you know,
in the in the in the Excel sheet.
It's not here.
Yeah.
Yeah, so, so this is a high level.
the background on this.
So any questions on this,
the dashboard requirement?
So I'm kind of,
I'm still somewhat new to some of these
requests and things like that. So the...
Yes.
Mhm.
My understanding was that our migration
would keep two separate dashboards where
we would still have an internal dashboard
and an external dashboard where the
internal pulls from the DTP data,
which is still being migrated,
and the external pulls from this FSP type
data.
So, uh.
Is the request here that everything be
merged into a single dashboard that
represents both the internal and external
tickets?
So, you ask me, yes, as a URI requirement,
because right now, right,
I have to go to two different dashboard
here.
And some of this, right,
if let's say I have all these tickets,
right, from internal, from external,
and also from internal,
in the same dashboard, right,
it's easy for me.
But the problem is that because of the
limitation of and the restriction of the
current architecture, I'm not able to.
for some reason, right?
So that's why I have two maintaining 2
dashboards, right?
Because Nirmala has its own dashboard,
which is powered by BI. I am,
my dashboard is powered by native JSM.
Okay? And they are different. So,
you know,
it's good to standardize and make it one
single source is easier for us to
maintain.
But, you know,
but I'm not sure whether it's feasible.
So, to me, yes, you ask me.
That should be the goal.
Okay. Is this, I guess when was,
is this a new requirement or is this
Okay.
something that you guys have been
requesting for a while now?
I, I have been so, yeah,
but but it was you were told I was told
that I'm not able to,
because DTP deal there have been two
instances.
And each of them have their own.
The problem is that there are a lot of
other things to work,
because they have their own SLA too.
They are not, you know,
so it's kind of messy.
So, can I ask a question here?
Uh-huh.
So, um, now I understand why I'm here, um,
so...
Who accesses the dashboard?
Me, whoever, okay, let me show you. No,
no, no, executive. Let me, okay,
Only you, you're the only person.
let me have, go, go,
maybe walk you through since, yeah.
Well, okay, let me ask you this question.
Will everyone at TTP be able to see the
combined dashboard?
Yes,
I think there's no reason why they should
Yeah, that's going to be a problem.
not.
Yes.
We have to keep boundary services.
Information,
because it may contain customer
information separate.
That's why they would have set it up this
way.
Yes, I understand.
And a combined dashboard may be
inconvenient for you,
but we can't let everyone at EDP see
Foundry Services Jira dashboard.
What's the reason behind that?
There is a requirement to keep Foundry
Services customer information separate
Oh.
from the rest of Intel's business,
especially in anything for Intel product
Bum.
groups.
Have you taken the Foundry Services
customer information training class?
No, I understand that. I have training.
I understand that. So I'm saying that who,
If, if not, you should.
Yeah,
that's the training that says that has to
be separate.
who, who has, I know who.
So YT and James, right? Here's the thing,
right? Data reporting part, right?
Mhm.
James has the valid point.
This has been discussed in past also in
this forum.
Data on the data warehouse side or the
Mm.
data analytics side can decide,
but who accesses that still need to be
governed by access control.
Yes.
A person who doesn't have access to the
actual project, underlying project,
should not be able to see it on the
report as well.
Yes.
Absolutely. If they have access,
they should be able to access the
information, right?
And then it should be controlled by AGS,
OK, so.
right? So...
So you're saying the dashboard will look
different depending upon the person's HES
The two pictures on the content.
access?
That's the expectation.
Yes.
OK, then then you'll just have to submit,
you know, that IP protection plan,
Yes, so, for example...
Hey, Cortana, play the song.
and let's see if it meets the requirement
of the data separation. It might.
And then we do work through a little bit.
Ideally, as we are talking about it,
we want to bring up all the way from
Is go by project, is go by project, right?
So, is admitted by AGS, right? If,
I'll give you that.
for example, right, this is, for example,
I have, let's say, 18 in.
there.
Right,
I have access to all these projects here.
This is my dashboard, OK?
And this dashboard I have access to.
We have a question.
This project.
Right, the same dashboard.
Maybe others for others may not have
access to this if they don't have access
to this project and it's all controlled
by AGS.
Yep,
and the access approval is the project
Yes.
owners, right?
Yes, yes, it's all controlled, right? So,
so if let's say someone in DDP,
Tool.
I'm partnering with him to support Intel,
right?
Uh-huh.
They should have the same information to
collaborate with customer and assess the
Mhm.
information, right?
Because we are in the same team.
Okay.
Does that under the question?
Okay.
No. Because I'm not that familiar with it.
We'll need to have you submit the IP
I'm sorry, why?
I think it's...
protection plan to IFO and get Mahesh and
Henrik to look at it and review the,
especially Mahesh.
She's going to be way more familiar with
Yeah, De.
how JIRA is managed and
what information is available.
Mahesh Nayyar, right? You say?
Mahesh, yes.
Yeah, yeah.
So Mahesh Nayyar was in this forum, right?
I think he's invited here. He's out.
He had called it out as an ask also.
And this ask again, higher,
you have captured it also in one of your
previous meetings.
As long as data is protected by the same
Perfect.
access governance.
when the report is built,
it should be good,
but we can recapture that as an item and
get a reconfirmation.
But the access is for record level
security, row level security,
The.
Yeah.
just to reiterate, right,
to hire and Mark,
I.
because Mark is new to this work group.
Right. Ideally,
they don't even see the list, but...
They want a list.
You can talk to Mahesh about whether or
not they can see the list or not is OK.
E.
When you say list.
List of list of projects.
Yeah, ideally they... Okay. Okay.
No, they will not. They will not.
They will not. They will not see the list.
No, they will not. As I said, right,
if you don't have the, yes,
They should not.
I have access to all this because I've
been given the access through AGS.
If you don't have access to this,
this will not come in.
Correct.
The ask is for record level security and
Yes.
Mahesh Nayyar was in this call.
And just for your note, right, Mark, yeah.
OK,
just make sure you close that AR with him.
It's already discussed and captured in
one of your meeting notes, Hayer,
Yeah.
Yes.
but maybe you want to recapture it and
say that, you know,
Mhm.
we are agreeing on a row level security
and access will be governed by the
underlying access of the system.
And that's where I think Mark and hire,
you may want to reiterate it.
And then when you're building the report,
you'll have to take that into account.
Someone has to write this down and let
Mahesh review it,
ask his questions and agree that his IP
control concerns are taken care of.
So, so I think...
Verbal won't work.
Meeting minutes won't work.
No, no, no, no, no, James,
that's what I'm trying to say, right?
I agree.
Someone needs to write it down.
He was in the call.
The discussion happened when Iyer
presented,
but that's why I'm saying let's recapture
it because it was already discussed when
this original meeting started. Yes.
Oh, okay.
So can you send a document to me for the
IP controls?
So, Iyer,
I think it was in one of your initial
presentations that you had captured it.
Yeah, that's right.
We discussed this part of the part of the
If you can.
security. Let me find that meeting notes,
James, Chris, sorry,
and I will send it with you. Okay.
Yeah, meeting us won't be enough,
discussion won't be enough.
Someone has to write it down and Mahesh
has to write off on it,
say he approves it.
It doesn't have to be complicated.
The meeting note captures, no, no James,
that's what he's saying.
Yes, of course.
Meeting notes captures the discussion
that happened and he had given a
confirmation.
What else are you looking for?
He was in the meeting.
His notes were the ones which were
captured.
Are you saying that you want him to write
a specific verbiage?
I'm surprised that he gave an oral
approval, but it's his to manage.
I wouldn't do that.
I would have required someone to do a
Okay, that's.
Okay.
write-up of here of the IP controls,
and then before I approve.
Okay.
So, so, so, so, may I?
But that's just me.
Who's A stakeholder here, you know,
who's the?
Good, Amit.
And, and I'm just covering for Mahesh,
okay? He's out on sabbatical.
Yeah.
He'll be back on Monday.
Okay. Oh, you are from the IP office?
So, so.
Yes, yes, I'm I'm at this coverage here.
Unfortunately, I know nothing about Jira.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, Chris is from the IP.
Okay, okay. Yeah, let's,
maybe we are all talking the same thing
But I do know about IP protection.
So, so...
because there was verbiage and everything
written in the PowerPoint. Let's hire,
Yeah.
Perfect.
why don't you share that and then you
know we can reconfirm.
So, so I, Jr.
I assume this has been resolved already,
Yeah, sounds good.
I think, right, access control, right,
is not an issue, right?
I think having this dashboard, right?
The.
I didn't hear a concern,
but since James is bringing it up,
And then, yes, OK, let's move on, yeah,
yeah, because, OK.
But I will tell you this,
I'm glad I know because I mapped out the
there's no harm in closing it. Yeah.
All right.
JIRA ticketing processes for Henrik for
Foundry Services customer information and
we said it was separate.
And so I'm glad I know because I got to
go back and update my documentation that
it.
E.
Upon this change.
So, okay, can we move on? I think,
all right, I think, yeah, Mark,
Yeah.
since we have this,
I just want to let you know,
If it's...
kind of a glance,
the feel of the dashboard,
what we intend to do here. Basically,
we're tracking all the tickets that's
coming in to all this project, right?
For example, let's say for example,
Last one year,
ticket harmony created these are all the
status, right?
It helps us to track the status, right?
And then we're using this also with a
customer, with customer,
the customer has access to through the
following portal.
you know, all these tickets, right?
And then secondly,
we also monitor and track the SLA
performance for the KPI.
So we have 5 KPIs. Sorry, sorry.
So first one is the conformal index,
Thank you.
No, go ahead.
right? For example,
our SLA is one day to acknowledge.
The tickets, right? So,
this is the performance, right? So,
the past SLA, so you know,
we're tracking all this, right?
The percentage,
and then for resolution we have
showstopper, severity high, medium,
and low for each of these.
They have their own SLA, right?
For showstopper, it's three days, right?
And this is a performance trend.
So we track this and then so forth,
all right?
So, basically,
the gist of this is a gist of dashboard,
OK.
Okay, let me tell you very quickly,
WaiChee, on this one.
OK?
Okay, go ahead.
I know that Gabriel also is working in
some thing here in the Jira dashboard.
In the part of that Windows in,
we can do it, okay?
Mm.
We can extract the data from the PP and
generate our own dashboard in Power BI
Okay, good.
and generate the permission stuff,
all that stuff. But when we took this,
Gabriel,
myself also some one month and a half ago,
Mm.
probably.
MM mm.
We discussed this part that alternative
to make available to have this dashboard
finally in Jira.
Mhm.
In my point of view regarding for the
data permission, the migration,
and all the stuff that we need to program
in Power BI, in my,
I think it's better to have this
dashboard in JITA.
And you mean in Jira?
I mean this this dashboard is in Jira.
In case that is already done,
why we are needed to generate the
dashboard in Power BI?
Because...
Okay, okay, okay.
I have the same question too, right?
Okay.
So I tried to replicate this, basically.
I tried to replicate this to here.
I couldn't,
because they don't allow me assessed SLA,
first of all. Okay?
And then they don't have the custom,
for example, they don't have a budget.
In what if there's a third party?
Custom is a custom native plugin, right?
First of all,
Plug in, plug in.
I think the main to the showstopper is
that.
SLA.
They don't allow us to access the SLA
because we need, for us,
for me to generate this,
we need the SLA data. First of all,
they don't allow anybody outside DDP to
access SLA. And secondly,
it's more like a resource issue.
They need a plug-in,
they don't have funds to it, so I gave up.
I push, I push, so, so I agree with you,
right? I agree with you, right?
Mhm.
So, this is from AleX, right?
This is from Alex and team,
Chee.
Carrie and team that they said.
Yes, Carrie, yes. So I totally agree,
right? Is in native, right?
It should be in Power BI, right?
And although the native GSM, right,
the dashboard, right,
is not as flexible as Power BI in terms
of, you know, the user, right,
the flexibility, right? But
I...
It serves the purpose of me able to,
you know,
track all the tickets and all the SLA
performance real time.
So I can just go in, right,
which I can just go in here and then just
hold it and then just go deep dive into
which are the tickets that's passing and
not passing. And that's what I want.
So question,
you do not want to see internal and
external dashboard together in one view.
No, you should be too. You should be too.
That is never going to happen if it is
built into separate systems,
Yeah.
Yeah, yes, that's why, yes, correct. So,
so I mean,
unless it is through an analytics release.
that's why we have two dashboards here,
right?
The reason why I come up with these two
dashboards, right, initially,
It.
I FS is in Power BI, is in Power BI,
but it is nowhere near where we are right
now. So, and then the administrator, Juho,
has left.
There's no administrative lab,
so I have no choice but to come up with
my own dashboard on JSM,
and we come to this point that we have,
I have a dashboard that is functional,
right? I'm very happy with this, right?
So I can actually go in here, I see, well,
well,
Yeah.
what are the tickets that are failing
here? I can just go in here, see?
I just go in, Ops, this is, yeah.
So it's functioning. So this dashboard,
right, is more for executive too, right?
Any executive coming in, right,
he wants to know how well are we doing in
the SLA, right? You can see it here,
right? Very fast.
Mm.
It serves the functions already. So I,
they are, I, you know, the,
where else if I look at the Power BI
dashboard in DDP, okay, it's very busy.
It's not as clear cut as this.
So I would love to convert this to here,
Right.
Jalihal.
Uh-huh.
True.
Yeah.
I think Gabriel too, right?
I think easy for us to maintain.
No.
Yeah, yen.
No,
I don't think that part we brought it up
M.
Mmh.
with Alex when we met on Monday, right?
Yeah,
maybe if you are okay with two different
dashboard, it saves a lot of work,
maintenance and everything, right?
Because once you move data, right,
it is maintenance, it is work.
Yeah, so that that that that's fine. So,
so if that's the case, right? I,
if you know it's not so, my, I, my, my,
the other approach is that from here,
right?
If I look at here, right,
so as long as all the tickets that I can,
that coming in, right, per project, right,
is within this here.
all tickets coming in here and then we
escalate to DDP, that's okay.
So I can monitor all the tickets.
The problem is that there's some, yes,
On BTP.
on the IFS side, right?
So at least I don't even have to look at
this here.
I know any tickets coming internally.
It's within inside here and actually
through DDP, right?
Yeah.
And these two guys talk, right?
As long as I have the ticket residing
here, it's okay.
Because the problem is right now, right?
I have tickets coming in here and tickets
coming in here for the same project.
Yeah.
And I need to.
two different dashboards to track.
So that's very confusing, right?
But.
So that's why I think Vijay has been
pushing, right, the escalate, right,
Yeah.
because we have so many accelerate
programs,
make sure that we have a bridge here so
all tickets can be initiated here.
So let me clarify it. The bridge is not,
the bridge is being asked not to create
And then, and then there's okay.
tracking.
The bridge is truly asked because you do
not want to create a ticket a second time
when it's a customer ticket that needs to
Yes, Dustin.
be assigned to an internal system,
correct? Okay.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yes, yes,
but it it serves the purpose of this
having one ticket in one, right? Yeah,
yes, yes, correct, correct. So,
Yeah, indirectly, yeah, yeah, yeah,
it does, yes, yes.
that's why Vijay has been pushing it,
right?
And then the other sub program that we're
doing here,
And...
because we don't have an internal
ticketing system right now,
and then Gabriel is still working on this,
right?
And then we don't have an internal ticket
system, right,
that because right now any tickets that
are coming in, right,
customer has visibility to this, right?
Sometimes for the same project, right,
we don't want customer to have visibility
on this, right? We want to have, yeah.
I put.
But for the internal system, right,
I thought there was a solution that was
proposed by Bharat, right, Gabriel?
So, that, that's the, so yeah,
what is the status for that, Gabriel?
Yeah,
that one I need to give you guys a
feedback.
Remember I shared some like some
screenshots or some diagram and then we
had some questions so we needed so we had
Yeah.
or I have a like a working POC in
pre-prod so that we can collect the
feedback again and see if.
This is the way that we will be setting
it up, or if...
No, it's okay. I thought we say we agree,
right?
Based on your solutions is proposed by
you, as long as it meets our requirement,
it's okay with us, right?
I don't care what the architecture,
it all depends how much you want to,
what are the resources you need to
maintain that system, right?
As long as it meets our requirement,
the internal system,
Basically,
the internal ticket is exactly the same
external.
It's just that the only except the only
difference is that customer don't have
the visibility to it. That's it. Yeah,
At this, yeah.
Mhm, mhm.
that's it, right?
Maybe you should schedule a demo then
there.
Okay, yeah.
Yeah.
Yeah, I will. I yeah,
I'll probably invite I see like you,
Yeah.
Raman,
and all the folks that initially
yen.
requested it,
so that we can have a quick walkthrough
of the of the model,
so that then we can move this to
production.
So, to answer your question, right,
I don't know how, whether it's feasible,
you know,
is this is this wishful thinking to have
the same dashboard?
I wish it could be is not,
but I'm prepared that, you know,
we have two different dashboard here,
you know, they have their own requirement,
but I'm perfectly happy with the
dashboard that I have here.
And I have making sure all the internet
external tickets are inside here. OK, so..
.
Okay,
I think we have a good understanding of
the problem statement, right?
Yes, I hope so. Any question, let me know.
OK, very well. So,
let's let's we need to land in this this
part, right?
Because we have a lot of time talking
about this dashboard,
so and and I understand very well the
part of the requirement on that.
Let's this makes push harder.
I I will discuss.
with Mark and making all the background
that we have ready for the external Jira
dashboard are the ones that we have some
progress already.
And then we can continue development on
the conversation on this part.
I hope WaiChee we need to take a decision
next week. We cannot let continue having.
this discussion about the DTP stuff.
The only thing that right now is an
stopper is a migration and we received
the information from the team that they
Mhm.
will finish work with 36,
something like that. But for that one,
Okay, okay.
we need to have ready the point.
So let me work on that and also working
Yeah.
with you and your availability for
example.
Yeah, yeah.
With Mark to make this happen, OK?
Yes.
Yes, correct. So,
so I'll be off next week until September
Okay.
1st, so alright, so just let you know.
Okay, no problem at all.
Let me discuss internally.
All the information that you provided for
this one and the previous goals is very
Yeah.
valuable. So Mark,
do you need anything else for the
Thank you, yeah.
requirements for WaiChee?
I think I just need to rehash this
discussion with someone directly.
There's a lot of background here that I'm
not as familiar with. What are the actual,
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I don't, from all the discussion here,
I didn't get a clear statement of what
our decisions are moving forward for the
dashboards.
Like,
is the decision here that we do keep a
separated internal external dashboard
right now,
and we want a Power BI dashboard as
opposed to just sticking with the JSM
dashboard that WaiChee has been using so
far?
So,
let's let me make sure that we don't we
have the correct terminology, right?
These are all to me,
there's only two the JIRA,
the external dashboard is the IFS, right?
The internal dashboard you're talking
about is the DTP, is that right? Okay.
Right, but,
but internal could be different too,
right? Internal could be,
as I mentioned just now, right?
There is another internal.
Ticket portal that we are trying to bring
up, which is different from the external,
that it only different that the customer
do not have visibility to it, so please,
please differentiate this, but this, this,
yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey, hey, I just joined. Yeah,
let's make sure when we use the internal
Actually.
dash internal versus a partner
organization, right?
So that's what WaiChee you're trying to
say, right? Internal meaning, you know,
Yes.
Did the pin?
like we can have a Gabriel, you know that,
right? Internal.
Yeah.
that we are trying to create versus,
you know, like for example,
ADG has a internal JIRA system for all
the ADG related tickets internally that
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
we can assign each other and manage that.
So that is internal to me.
Then, then, yeah, for yes.
But with the bridge stuff that we are
talking about is from external JIRA to.
Partner organizations - that's very clear,
right? Every Jeena and Iyer, and yeah,
Yes, yes, yes, yeah,
we we should just confine, yeah,
we should just make sure, yeah.
and then Gabriel - is it? It's very clear,
right? The terminology.
Mark.
For this, for this discussion,
we just stick to IFS is the external,
right? For internal,
you should talk to to mention this DD
point to DDP to minimize any confusion.
Yeah,
I think that's the terminology I've been
trying to use is internal means the DTP
side, external means the IFS side, right?
Okay.
If I need to change my terminology,
let me know, but the...
Yep.
Yeah,
but the internal could be a different,
as I mentioned,
and now we mentioned the internal could
be a different order that that Gabriel is
trying to bring up,
so which is different from the DTP.
Okay, I'm not as familiar with that site.
So right now my understanding is just
OK, yeah, yeah, OK, OK, yep, you're right,
correct.
this external is this Foundry Services
portal,
Yep, correct.
the internal is this DTP customer portal,
right? And my understanding so far,
It would be.
Yes, yeah, yeah.
or my previous alignment,
was that we would have two separate Power
BI dashboards,
one of them representing the external for
the Foundry Services portal.
Mm.
which is what I have a live working
version of right now.
Mhm.
And then there would be an internal one
for the DTP portal side,
which is gated by the DTP migration,
which is slated right now for work week
36. Is that right?
Yeah, yeah,
I I think based on the discussion just
now, yeah, you brought up right,
even on the the external right,
the IFS right, the dashboard right,
should it be in Power BI or should we
just we just use the the the native JSM
right that we're using?
I prefer Power BI, right? You know,
the native is, yeah,
native is very restrictive. You know,
I would like to see what Mark's proposal
Yes.
What do you mean with it?
for using the Power BI for external.
Well, I think my...
I'm okay.
My proposal has been to just follow the
requirements given by WaiChee, right,
Yes, yes, so, yeah.
which is recreating the...
OK, OK,
so you said you have created already,
Yeah, yeah.
Dashboard thing that he's been saying
there, right?
But it's the same extent, but...
Mark.
Is it is it is available now from your
Is the same.
from you?
Mhm.
one with WaiChee to clarify some of those,
but there's a V1 of it available now.
Yeah.
I see.
So that's configurable to any projects.
Let's say YG has 20 projects and he can
configure that and then I have totally
different 15 projects and I can configure
that in the V1 version.
Yeah,
there are slicers available for project
where you can go in and select what you
want.
And if we want to do like pre-selections
for different teams,
I think we could do that as well, right?
Can you include me in meeting with
WaiChee?
I'm an equal stakeholder for this
external Jira and DDP Jira.
Sure, I can forward the meeting.
And Mark,
before you grant access to anybody,
please make sure that the row level
access or record level access is honored
because I don't think YG and Nirmala has
access to all projects and so is no quora.
Yeah, so that's.
No, not necessarily.
We don't have access to each other
projects, no.
Yeah, so higher, this is a big concern,
right?
Yeah, yeah.
The V1 does not have RLS because it was
not a requirement, right?
So I don't know if we want to push this
meeting until I get something implemented
I did.
there,
but I'm a little nervous by the
discussion that we had about RLS.
Yeah.
But Jeena, if I remember,
Vijay was stipulating that to create a
dashboard,
it should not be restricted per access.
The reason is, for example,
say central organization like DTP, right?
They want to look at the as a whole,
you know,
Mm.
they don't necessarily have access to all
these projects, so, but they want to know.
Correct,
they should not be then seeing the
Yeah.
project names and that obfuscation should
happen, right? Because the key is the key,
Okay, I don't know. I yeah.
like,
because when we are when we were
discussing this with Mahesh on the call,
right?
He was also saying there are roomed
projects.
You're talking with respect to your
access, right? So today, if I go,
Mm.
I will also see everything,
whereas I don't have any production
Yeah.
access.
to any projects.
So there are people who have relatively
Yeah.
access to everything.
They are maybe very few and far in
between. But once you open up for,
once it's not there, it's not there.
It's out there, right?
And then it's a liability.
Okay, so room I know,
room projects we should not get,
minus the room, right?
So let's say the minus room projects.
Let me ask in a different way, right?
If truly there is no access data,
why is the application restricting it too?
Why can't we open it up for all Intel
users?
Why are we saying that you can go from
Buss.
the reporting and see the data and not
from the application and see the data?
No, no, I think it's more from the, like,
you know, KPI and a performance, you know,
for that type of information from
organization standpoint,
what Vijay was saying, but anyway,
this needs a broader discussion.
I don't have time right now, but we can,
yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yes. Row level, yeah,
row level access was needed as per this
thing of what who can see.
It should be governed by the underlying
application.
That part was a miss in the other project.
Okay, yeah, yeah, right, right, right.
Today,
I'm interested first of all the V1 at V1
level for the projects I have access.
E.
I know I should be able to create the
dashboard.
That's my current big requirement.
So anyway, we give,
I'll meet with you guys, Mark, whenever.
Meeting with the WaiChee, and yeah.
Yeah,
to follow up this capture of the
requirements,
then it's another topic and the site
security,
I will copy the one that we discussed
already and the one that we agreement in
the mini notes.
Let's review next week and in case that
we need to follow up any change there,
okay?
All right. Thank you.
Yeah, I think I need,
I still need a high level decision here,
right?
So we have a meeting scheduled basically
for right now,
and the V1 that I have has no row level
Right now.
security applied, right?
So do we need to push until I get some
Okay, so Mark.
RLS on this report,
or what is the decision here?
I would recommend to put RLS.
We want to.
Unless you want to do a demo with test
projects and you know you're doing that
So I think I think it's like we are not
rolling this out, right?
way, that's fine.
You just have a first look, right?
So to go through our requirements, right?
We are not rolling this out. It's okay to,
right?
Ohh, yeah, yeah, one second, Mark, can,
can you?
Yeah, I mean it is live now though, right?
Do I need to pull it down and have an
Hi.
offline version only? Or what is the...
When you say live,
does anybody have access to it other than
No.
Yeah.
you, Mark?
Whoever has access to the IFS Dart
location, right?
Hey, I need to join the meeting.
Please push out this by one hour or
Maybe I can talk with you offline and
then yeah.
No.
something, Mark. I don't mind.
Yeah.
Let me ping you offline, Mark.
Yeah.
Hello?
Yep, yep.
Yeah, do you?
Yeah, so let me know. So I'm okay. I mean,
whether you're ready,
I'm ready to go through with you,
have a first load. So I'm off next week.
So if not, we just wait until I come back.
Okay.
Yeah, I, I, let's.
WaiChee,
give me 5 minutes to have a quick call
with Jeena,
and then I'll jump over to the other
Okay.
meeting that we have scheduled for the
external issue dashboard review.
Yeah, Nirmala,
Nirmala has already started the meeting.
And we can chat there.
Yeah, I saw that. Yeah,
just let her know that I'll be there in a
Yep.
OK, alright, bye.
few minutes.
All right, thanks.
Google.